insurance company FWD group is closing
down one component of its business group
medical insurance in Singapore it says
some 80,000 people are expected to be
affected by the move
following queries FWD Singapore said it
has decided to focus on and allocate
more investment in resources to other
lines of its business that will support
stronger growth in the future
these include its Direct and online life
and general insurance offerings the
employee benefits of business will
therefore wind down by the end of next
year
this insurer is believed to be the fifth
largest group medical insurer in the
country it has almost 400,000 customers
across its insurance products and added
that its clients were informed last
month on the closing of the business
through methods such as it calls and
face-to-face chats and is speaking to
the affected staff and figuring out the
next steps for them FWD entered the
Singapore market in 2016 and started off
providing employee benefits insurance to
corporate customers